myffpc.com 2019-12-17

# Privacy Policy | FFPC

FFPC recognizes that individuals who play in FFPC leagues and contests value their privacy. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the collection, use and disclosure of user information collected on FFPC league management platform, located at [www.myffpc.com](http://www.myffpc.com/).

This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with our [Terms and Conditions](https://myffpc.com/ffpccontent/trust/terms-conditions/). By registering for a FFPC player account, or participating in any FFPC leagues and contests, or using the FFPC league management platform in any manner, you accept this Privacy Policy and the policies described herein.

Any questions, comments or complaints that you might have should be emailed to [info@myffpc.com](mailto:info@myffpc.com). You may also send it by mail to:

FFPC  
FFPC, LLC  
1133 Broadway, Suite 539  
New York, NY 10010

FFPC requires all its customers to maintain an account accurate and current personal information such as name, email, address of residence, and phone number.

When a customer deposits funds into their account, we also receive certain payment information which is handled and stored securely by Authorize.net, the online credit card payment gateway. FFPC does not have access to, nor does it store credit card numbers in its software or on its servers.

FFPC is highly sensitive to the need to protect user information and secure their online accounts. FFPC uses multiple methods to ensure that all customer data and account balances are protected at all times. FFPC’s system and data are hosted at a reputable data center located in the United States. The application sits behind a firewall. Web traffic that includes credit card or purchase information leverages https (2048-bit encryption) and Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software while in transit. In addition, all users’ passwords are encrypted using a one-way hash and salted.

FFPC uses the information collected send service, news and product announcements, newsletters, and advertisements. Information like emails and phone numbers are also used to assist customers with various customer service issues, but typically for no other purposes. FFPC uses cookies to maintain login information.

FFPC does not offer services or sell products to minors. FFPC does not request or knowingly collect personally identifiable contact information from anyone under the age of 18.

FFPC is committed to protecting our customer’s personal information and does not share any such information with anyone with the following exceptions.

FFPC will send or share personal information with other companies or people when:

  * we have the customer’s consent to share the information
  * we need to share personal information to provide a product or service a customer has purchased or requested
  * we need to send personal information to companies who work on behalf of FFPC to provide a product or service to you, or who provide a service used by FFPC, such as BigGameSoftware.com, Footballguys.com or Electronicverificationsystems.com
  * we need to share personal information with third parties (such as banks and credit card processors) to the extent necessary for FFPC to deliver payment processing services.
  * we are required to comply with law; enforce or apply our Merchant Agreement and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of FFPC, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and risk reduction.

FFPC is committed to helping its customers to stay protected against unauthorized access to their FFPC player accounts. Please sign off when finished using a shared computer and otherwise protect the password used to access FFPC player accounts.

FFPC reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. If a revision to the Privacy Policy is material, the FFPC will notify you by contacting you through the email address associated with your player account.
